fitnessrepublic.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy | Fitness Republic

Fitness Republic (” **Company** “) respects the privacy needs and concerns of our customers. Any personal information, such as your name, address, email address or phone number (” **Personal Information** “) is important to us. We respect your privacy in handling Personal Information relating to you and your transactions with us through fitnessrepublic.com (” **Website** “).

When you provide Personal Information to us, in any way or through any medium (e.g. customer service, Website, tec.), you are consenting to the manner in which Company may collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your Personal Information, which is set forth herein.

**Permission to Use This Website** . The Website is not intended or designed to be used by anyone under the age of 13. Company does not collect Personal Information from any person it knows to be under the age of 13. If you are under 13, DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE AND DO NOT SEND ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION. IF YOU ARE BETWEEN THE AGES OF 13 AND 17, DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE UNLESS YOU ARE SUPERVISED BY A PARENT/GUARDIAN OR HAVE RECEIVED PERMISSION FROM YOUR PARENT/GUARDIAN.

DO NOT SEND US INFORMATION UNLESS YOU CONSENT TO THE APPLICATION OF U.S. LAW AND TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION CONSISTENT WITH THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.

**Collection of Personal Information.** We may collect Personal Information that you provide us when you: purchase, order, return, exchange or request certain information about our products and services; contact customer service; register with the Website or participate in another feature of our Website that requires your Personal Information; provide us with comments, suggestion or social media posts.

We may also collect Personal Information about you from our third party service providers who provide us with e-commerce and/or technical related associated with functionality and purposes of the Website.

When you purchase products and services through the Website, we will collect your credit or debit card information and keep a history of your purchases. We use this information to process your orders and to better assist you. We will also ask for your shipping information which may necessarily include your Personal Information. If your purchases are being shipped to you, your shipping information will be shared with our delivery service providers (e.g., U.S. Postal Service, UPS, or other delivery companies we or you select).

**Secure Shopping.** When you place orders on our Website, all of your order information, including your card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology causes your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our secure server. SSL technology, an industry standard, is designed to prevent someone other than operators of our Website from capturing and viewing your Personal Information. Since any order information you provide to us on our Sites will be transmitted using a secure connection, if your Web browser cannot support this level of security, you will not be able to order products through our Website.

**Passwords.** To provide you with an increased level of security, online access to your Personal Information is protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. Company will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (including unsolicited correspondence such as letters, phone calls or e-mail messages).

**Other Uses of Personal Information.** Company also uses Personal Information to continually assess and improve the products and services we offer. To serve you better, we may combine the Personal Information that you give us with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our marketing partners and others.

We would like to inform you of products and services, sales and special offers that might benefit you. When you register online, you will have the opportunity to sign up for e-mails about our products, services, sales and special offers. If you would like to stop receiving such promotional information from Company, please see the “Privacy Preferences/Opt-Out” section of this Privacy Statement.

**Third Party Access to Personal Information.** Some of our operations, such as website administration, technical support, and/or electronic commerce, may be managed by third parties unaffiliated with Company. These companies may share Personal Information with their affiliates and with service providers whom they engage to perform services related to our Website or the operation of our business.

**Legal Proceedings.** If Company or any of our service providers is requested by law enforcement officials or judicial authorities to provide Personal Information on individual users, Company or the applicable service provider may, without your consent, provide such information. In matters involving claims of personal or public safety, Company or the applicable service provider may provide your Personal Information to appropriate authorities without your consent or court process. Company or our Service Providers also will provide your Personal Information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or in litigation involving Company, the applicable service provider, or otherwise as required by law. We may also disclose Personal Information to assist in debt collection where you owe a debt to us.

**Privacy Preferences / Opt-Out.** If you wish to Opt-Out from any of the aforementioned uses of Personal Information, except in the case of Legal Proceedings, please contact us via email at [ info@fitnessrepublic.com ](mailto:info@fitnessrepublic.com) Your subsequent disclosure of Personal Information nullifies any prior Opt-Out request.

**California Resident Information Sharing Disclosure Requests.** If you are a California resident, you have the right to request one Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure per year which will identify the third parties with whom Company or any of our affiliates has shared thePersonal Information we have collected from you. You may request the Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure by writing to us at Fitness Republic, Account Service, 545 Fifth Avenue, 6th Floor, New York, New York 10017, Attn: Privacy Manager. We will respond to your request for a Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure within 30 days.

**Cookies.** Our Website uses “cookies”. A cookie is a tiny element of data that our Websites can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize your computer when you return. Cookies also assist with performance of various aspects of the Website. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. However, should you decide not to accept cookies from our Website, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Website.

**Security.** We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of Personal Information in our custody and control. We also are committed to employing reasonable technology in order to protect the security of our Website. However, even with the best technology, no website is 100% secure.

**Outside Links.** This Privacy Statement only applies to the Website. The Website may include links to the websites of our business partners, vendors and advertisers. These other sites are outside of our control. Please be aware that these websites may collect information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices which may differ from those contained in our Privacy Statement.

**Modification to Privacy Statement.** From time to time we may modify or amend this Privacy Statement in order to comply with new laws or regulations or to reflect future changes in our business practices. Any changes in our policies will be communicated in this page so please check back on occasion.

**Contacting Us.** If you have any questions about our handling of Personal Information, please contact us at [ info@fitnessrepublic.com ](mailto:info@fitnessrepublic.com)
